{
    "id": "f750e39ca1d947d7b1a99cb856620fd0",
    "title": "All, Every Or Whole",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3050e3ba2e9b47a0a6f79f7c31d76505",
            "title": "All, Whole Or Every",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I spent the ……………………………… in bed.",
                    "description": "The article goes before whole.",
                    "answers": [
                        "whole day",
                        "all day",
                        "whole the day"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I spent ……………………………. the week with my parents.",
                    "description": "We use all or all of before a noun with a determiner. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "all of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was here ………………………………..",
                    "description": "All day means from morning to night.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all day",
                        "whole day",
                        "every day"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was here …………………………………… of the week.",
                    "description": "Every day means Monday to Sunday.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all day",
                        "every day",
                        "every the day"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Suddenly ……………………………… went out.",
                    "description": "All and all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all the lights",
                        "all of the lights",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………….. Paris was talking about their affair.",
                    "description": "All Paris means all parts of Paris.",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "All the",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have invited ………………………………. friends.",
                    "description": "All and all of can both be used before a pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all my",
                        "all of my",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have invited ……………………………….. I have.",
                    "description": "Before a singular noun we use every.",
                    "answers": [
                        "every of friend",
                        "every friend",
                        "all friend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents lived their ………………………………. in Mexico.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "all life",
                        "whole life",
                        "whole life"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoy ……………………………… music.",
                    "description": "We cannot use every with uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "all of",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I spent ……………………………….. the afternoon at home.",
                    "description": "Instead of whole of, we generally use the whole of.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the whole of",
                        "whole of",
                        "the whole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your cat has drunk ………………………………….",
                    "description": "We use all of with most uncountable nouns. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "all the milk",
                        "all of the milk"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}